Would it be best for her to focus on those and then they're used to kind of flavor everything else? Or is this something we need to go through every single screen and then design it?
I said, I, you know, so here, let me, do I still have it up?
Yeah, so I'm actually playing on, so this is Claude Design. So I, since you gave me the B2B source, I pulled that in and was like, hey, let's build our design system around this B2B source. And so it pulled out, you know, pictures. Well, some of this is some of the newer stuff.
But it started pulling out like banners and sheets and chips and stuff like that. And so that was going to try and like recreate that on the opposing side. So basically having shown all this, if she can just get me like literally as we're doing, we can pick like the harder screens with like the most detail on them or the ones that she really wants to put her mark on, then it's easy enough for me to be like, hey, like here are those screens, fill in the middle.
like and it'll easily be able to do that sort of a deal. Because kind of as you've seen, which I don't know where that screenshot went now.
And then from there, Alex and I should be able to curate or fix or give recommendations on anything that we see that might be arrive based on what's created.
Yeah, perfect. So yeah, even here is where it tried to do, like I gave it the flow, like the PNG that I showed you a second ago, this one, where it shows the flows. I was like, hey, redesign this and just let me see what the flows look like. And so here is like it trying to do the flows. Here's like the invite first run flow. I just hit edit.
Okay.
So yeah, so there we go. So as I said, I could easily take her stuff, make this into an actual appropriate like thing and then go. So yeah.
Awesome.
Because, as we say, I deal, Bill, like, go ahead.
You never.
I was gonna say, we had another question come up as far as copy goes in our previous meeting with Matt and Abby, I was just meeting. At what point?
You know, obviously when we have something more final like this, we could go in and massage the copy so that it's in line with all of our branding, in line with everything we're saying out in the world. Is there a timeline for that? Is it something that we absolutely have to have it by this date and then there's no changes or is it something that's more fluid?
I mean, the sooner we can get that, the better is usually how it is, because then the app is just more flushed out as we go. But I mean, you know, we can obviously change artifacts as we go and improve them as they come in. I think honestly, if we just like lay this down, like the styling and retheme and stuff like that, we can easily just do as an ad hoc later.
What does?
But as I said, if we can get it as close as possible, I mean, that's my whole point of why I'm like pushing so much on the POC right now is so hopefully we can get this as close to MVP as possible. So then the team just always has something that you play with. Yeah.
That makes sense. And that's easy enough for us to turn around copy-wise. We're just looking for a timeline or, you know, right away, and we'll do it right away.
Yeah, definitely on the screens. I mean, the faster you can turn the screens around, that'll definitely help, especially for the ones, Christine, that you're asking, because it said that I can get the MVP up to date, which then helps the team on, you know, knowing like all of the features. I mean, for the most part, I feel like we have the features, so especially like today, we can go through, at least capture the features that we're thinking.
fully through, then I think we're all good as that, because the graphics we can go change later. Though sooner would be better as obvious.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Got it.
I won it yesterday. Now running through the app and where it's at, just so you guys can see it, and then we can go a little further. For whatever reason, it moved the logout to the top here. Again, we can change that whatever, but that's fine. I think you noticed, there's no longer the logout on the home screen. That was one of your feedbacks from yesterday that I was able to get finished. I probably didn't get all of them because it's been running non-stop.
He.
but we can only get so much in. So other than that, I think all this still works the same. As I said, if you want to come into here, you can also now remove people. This all works like perfect. So you can remove somebody, you can delete them from the wall. You can also add people to the wall, which
Oh, off to fix the add memory. Okay, so that doesn't work yet on that screen. You can know from when you come here, and this is what I was showing Eric yesterday. So like if we were wanting to come like a new test wall, if you just put the emails of the individuals that have already registered into this POC, they will show up on here.
be given the invite. So like create a wall. As I said, I don't have it sending an e-mail yet or doing anything like that to like get somebody into here. But now if we come into here, we log out and then we log in as my wife.
which I think I just clicked on myself again.
Oh, this is like the new user onboarding flow.
There's the screens again to where you can pick.
This was just an orange circle.
You can now hear it, re-record if you want, use that. I'll go ahead and put that on the first call.
Okay, cool. Who did I log in as? Yeah, I clicked on myself, so one second. I can't click, right?
Yap.
Click on Katie. All right, cool. So now Katie's coming into here. So now she's got her sketch a small thing on her desk today. So whatever she just drew.
I don't know, maybe she's got a cool cross.
And even though it shows up right here, which I'll fix that, that shouldn't show up right here.
Because I think we just created that new test wall. So yeah, so now it shows up in here. So now she's got her test wall. So now she's newly invited to it. Rob invited you. So now we come into here. So now here's, you know, Rob has invited you. And then I copied that picture because I thought it was cute. Accept and join. So now we get the regular flutter here. Click. Now she's going to draw something small on her desk.
As you can see now on the walls, I've updated to where now it has both the icons on the top. And this is more for Christina because I know Eric saw this yesterday. Yeah, like they revealed how you guys had it and your thing. And then obviously today, if we go look at some of the wall, that factor doesn't work right. So if we click on here,
And then we go to say this Forshier wall. Now you can start to see, so again, you got the stuff at the top. And then looks like there's, I think my scrolling is broken, so I can't scroll down, but you can be able to scroll through here. You can click on these now, which you already had that before. The new thing that was added was since I
remove the voice to text and kind of we had that separation of you can either have like a text story or a voice note. You either get the text story down here or you get in this case the voice note. So now you can hit play and then you hear that then voice note.
Um...
which that's actually modeling an IoT device that I built on my desk when I first was learning IoT. It's A 3 by 3 by 3 electronic cube that I built with it Arduino Nano. But yeah. Oh, and then something new that I told you I was working on, which finally wrapped up and worked yesterday, so you can come to the share screen. The share screen already worked.
But what didn't work was now you can hit share on here, and then if you go to like say notes, and I can hit save, and then let me grab my notes. You can also like have it copy out.
Sorry, I have 4 screens and trying to find my notes. Here's my notes.
And so then here is what then came in my notes. So you got sketch something small on your desk, which was the prompt for the day. And then like then it's got the thing and then it's, you know, I'll have to fix that one before it would show your actual like story. So I'll have to fix that because it's a voice note. So it shouldn't show up and it's got the little scribble logo on the bottom.
So that's like the outputting one that you guys wanted to prove that that one works.
Go ahead.
I was going to say that's awesome. That's good.
Okay, and it seems like it didn't put it in this one, but one thing that it had on like the local that was running was it used to have a section right above this revealed where it would say click on prompt pack. And then with that, it allows you then to like, it loads some screens where then you can see the prompt packs that you gave and you can kind of pick from them and then pick a prompt and then make it and it shows up.
for today. So that's something I'll just have to get fixed.
Yeah, I mean, this is pretty much like the run of the app. Now I can come in here and, you know, I can't approve it or put us hard on it because she can, but I can come into hers and put a hard on hers.
It works some of the times. I don't know why it's not working now, but yeah.
Right.
And from the last time you saw Christine, I, you know, I, they showed like putting all the stats in a box, that's what the stats got put in a box, and then it said all the flows, we removed the logout from here.
I think that was...
The majority of it, yeah, and then I clean up the theming, so now it's just light and dark, just so there's not too much. Again, make it whatever you want.
Yap.
Oops.
Much appreciate the dark world.
Yeah.
Does that does that follow device settings? Because I know some of my apps just automatic a little dark mode based on my device being very set to dark mode, or is that is that always manual?
That's something we can set. More than likely what we can do is we'll have the toggle, or we can have the toggle where it's like light, dark, or device setting. And that's usually what we have, and so at that point, but that would be, again, that would be in the customizations underneath the phone. So, but yes, we can do that.
OK.
And then for you, Christina, just so you know, and I mean, it should be self-explanatory, but there I added a toggle to the signup screen just so we can simulate new user onboarding. So we're not having to constantly add a new user every time to test that out. So it just makes it easier for us to test that out. So if you want to just test that out, like it's there, else like the next time you log in, it won't be there. So.
Got it. Thank you.
Yap.
So, yeah, so I mean...
Suren, did you have any questions? I know, oh, one thing that came up was sizing based on device.
Yap.
Um...
Correct. Do we have, like, are you, yeah, that was one of our questions on, like, what are the supportive, like, iPhone versions?
Is there is there a so I'll give an example.
At Dee's restaurant, she had a square system with an iPad in it, you know, that she used to check people out. And she came to me the other day and was like, oh, it says it can no longer update because this iPad hit end of life. And they're only updating these newly to, you know, from the 11 on or whatever it might be.
So is there a line in the sand when it comes to these devices that we say, okay, we design them for these in newer? And what is that line?
That's the point, Yap, that's the point, yeah.
Yap, and so that's where, yeah, you'll pick like, you know, I picked the last most recent 5 iPhones that are still supported by Apple, and so these are what we're going to support.
Okay, yeah, I think that's fine.
On the Android side, it's going to be a little bit more varied because it said that's kind of like, you know, Pixel, Samsung, you know, so that one, that one's a little bit more varied.
OK, so we'll focus on iOS, and when it comes to screen size, is it?
Possibly a stupid question. Is it cropping or is it shrinking? And what is the overall size that we should be shooting for? And it goes from there. Or are we creating an individual screen for every possible iPhone iteration in that lineup?
So I mean, usually they show up as rendered separately as separate like little pictures for each of the phones. So then we have, you know, the exact layout because their widths will be just slightly different. I mean, the nice thing about iOS is it's fairly generic across them. So I mean, for the most part, it's almost like it's just shrinking and kind of doing it. But one of the reasons why you kind of like lay that out is because, you know, from like the smaller iPhone to like the iPhone Max,
I mean, you're going to have a little bit more width in one of those areas. So you can like, you know, make your designs because you're giving us the separate designs. And if you wanted to, like, if there's, you know, nine colors, we could lay them out perfectly vertical, but then on the smaller phone, we might have to like double stack it. And so that's where you kind of like pick on that. And that's, you know, sort of like the exact same way of when you're picking like how big of like when you're doing like a web app and you're doing like the web bounding.
of when like you start to hit those activation points where now you can start to like stretch out tables or you have to shrink and reduce tables.
Christina, do you have any questions on like the screens we started picking out for you to work on or any questions in general?
I think, so it sounds like what you were saying, Rob, is that, just to clarify, it's really kind of up to us what screens we want to, I guess, provide you.
And like.
I know, Eric, you shared some. And then those will flavor, like, what you're building.
Is that right? Okay.
Exactly. Yes. So and that's what I was kind of like pointing out with this scribble design here is if you can give me like the harder screens or the screens with the more elements on it. So like I imagine like probably this login and logout screen, definitely the canvas, probably like the home screen.
maybe like the user one, you know, the key ones that have like the most things on it, I could, you know, then we have enough information to where like we can have it basically fill in the middle of like, you know, well, slash screen, that one's easy enough, like that doesn't really query, but like this would be easy enough to be like, oh, well, this is just like the button laid out, like they've laid out, they like the button here in this position, so we'll just.
Yeah.
Change the label, and then the text will look like this, and you know, so basically, as long as you can give me enough examples of everything, then the AI can just fill in the blanks.
Mhm.
Got it. Cool.
I think the splash screen, Christina, you'd probably want to handle that, right? We use our typical...
Um...
We.
I mean, I think it's already in some of the mockups, but getting the best version of our splash.
Like, yeah, yeah, and.
Eric, maybe we can talk just like a little bit generally about the design, the direction, and like how far we want to go from the B2B.
But yeah, yeah, maybe something closer to this.
Even, you know, even this, this, this is an MVP. We can stay pretty close to the B2B. We put a lot of work into that. White Spectre put a lot of work into that, so if it's if it's in the same realm, I think that's fine for this, and then you know, God willing, we have the opportunity to build this bigger and better, and...
Bringing some new design.
If it feels necessary.
Well, I do wonder, I know, like, my inclination.
is to simplify things. And like I know Matt kind of shared that opinion. Personally, I feel like the B2B is like...
Allegri.
I don't know. Some of like the color placement doesn't feel great to me. So I like even something like this feels a little bit closer to the direction of like it's simpler. It doesn't have these splashes of blue on every screen.
Does that sound like too far or okay, Eric?
No, no, I mean, that's obviously that's, you know, it's why you're here because you have these opinions and you know what's up. So we can also meet. No, I trust your opinion. So we can definitely, we can meet and go through everything and come up with something. I'd say yes, simpler is probably better for this.
It's just my opinion.
Okay.
Yap.
Yeah, and I I think I mean.
B2B is a bit saturated, but the B2B also has like a few less screens when it comes to, and it's also much bigger and there's like a lot more to play with. So I agree, simpler is better.
Yap.
Yeah, definitely cohesive. We can make it so it's cohesive, but I think if we can simplify this, it will be nicer.
Okay.
We still have 40 minutes. Do you guys want to go through the screens? And so, Christina, you can pick the screens and do the designs. I don't want to change much more after that because I feel like I'm making changes, then you guys are reviewing old changes and then wanting, you know, changes that I might have removed something. And so I don't want to make, you know, yeah, we're kind of all over the place, but now that like.
You know, I can give you guys the images because now it's like we have assigned style and everything, so like, here's everything. But like, are there changes right now to the app that you want me to make while still waiting for the designs? And then we can just kind of make sure that we're just in sync about that. So like as example, like on the settings screen, I already said like.
I don't like the placement logout, but if you guys like that, I can leave that there. Do we want to just like put a sticky note on there and say move this to the bottom?
Yes. Yeah, and if we want to shoot through each screen very quickly and just kind of give some quick feedback to make sure we're all in a good place, I think that's best.
Okay.
But yeah, that's why I just put this PNG up on the Lucid board, which I'll share this again. So again, if you guys want to make some comments, I just shared it in the chat. We can come in here and we can just add stickies to the board. And I said the nice thing is, go ahead.
And what I'm going to do copy, I was going to say what I'm going to do copywise on our end is simulate this for internally for the team so that we can start making suggestions, changes in real time and get you copy changes as soon as possible.
Beautiful, yes. Which is that, or if you want, if you want to just like put this on your Figma and then, because I know you gave me edit access now, although I think I tried to edit and it wouldn't let me. Or maybe I'm just not bright enough to know how to change things in here. But I mean, if you want, we can actually work in here right now since we're
Just now starting this, you have all the pictures. If you want to just do what I did there and just drop the big PNG on there, this flows one, then we can start doing the editing on your side.
Rob up.
because we don't have to do it inside of Lucid, we can do it inside of something you're more familiar with.
And I have no problems working inside of Figma.
Honestly, it was just the one I started working with and I liked it and...
I find it's a good...
It's a good compromise between the CAD programs that I was used to and very proficient in, and...
The Adobe stuff that I wasn't that great at.
So a lot, it's very numbers-based, which is what I like.
See, I love using Miro boards, like at my old company. I mean, I have built like, like our whole project on a Miro board where I just had like this ginormous board that the team could basically see everything, like even like it was a giant multi-teamed one. And so like even other teams, I'd put their stuff up there too if we were waiting on them. And it's like basically the team could like know.
like everything that was going on, who we were waiting on. So I've always loved Miro boards. That just, I would like to think, Miro boards.
Beautiful.
One question I had about, so the onboarding toggle, that's just for us now, so that we can show people that.
in the short term and demo, but that is something that would automatically be... Yes, okay.
Yep, yep, yep. That's just to make our lives easier, just like the like sign up screen having like the scrolling of names. Like otherwise, typing in your username and your password every every time you want to try something out is just a pain in the ***. So that's the reason why, yes, that's all for niceties.
And so...
I was asked that and that was my answer, but I just wanted to double check that I was giving people the right answer.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and and.
So.
I was gonna say, so for this login screen.
And also remember, as I said, this mobile app, I can also give you guys Android versions too. So if you guys really want to actually play with it on the phone, like I actually have been playing with it on my phone and my son loves drawing on this, just let me know because I can always spin one up and send the e-mail to you with a zip in it.
I am actually going to just pick up a spare iPhone so that I can be up to date in testing this in real time, but just Wi-Fi only and get service obviously. Is there a, I guess, is there a model, a latest or earliest model that I can get that will still be functional? Like where is that line that we're drawing?
For iPhones, we'd have to look that up.
Yap.
Basically, I don't want to spend $1500 on a brand new one if I can spend $300 on it only for one, but I don't want to get one that's two.
All right.
So...
I can bring this over here. But basically, right, so we're in 2026, which has the new iPhone 17s. So I mean, last year was 16. I mean, more than likely, we'll be supporting what they'll still support, which, okay, so it looks like they stopped supporting 2018. So what is that?
One, two, three, 4, 5, 6, 7. So it seems like they have about 7 years of support.
So I mean, to be truthfully honest, let's see, we're not using...
I think there's nothing on the device, because I mean, newer devices have like newer, fancier settings and abilities. I don't think there's anything new. So I mean, to be truthfully honest, like probably a 15 or 16 would work here, and those can be cheaper.
And so when we're also designing these screens, it's possible that we're going back to 2019 as far as sizing goes. A lot of that, there's probably going to be a lot of overlap though. Okay.
Right, yeah, yeah. And more than likely, like the iPhone 11 to 12 to 13 will have like the same resolution and size because they tend to keep like the models the same size. So building for the 12 would build for the 11 almost too. It's a lot of this, like mainly when you're supporting like the older devices, it's like the features and functionality. But as I said, since our app is so easy and it doesn't require like a fancy NPU or anything crazy, it's all just like...
like maybe a microphone and the screen, I think we're pretty good to just, you know, whatever that still works, that's still supported by Apple, we're still going to support.
Good info.
Then what's not on that is that I did get the output flow to work where it's generating that share. But as I said, we can drop that on there. As I said, remember, you guys do have access to the demo in Vercel, so you guys can also play with the
this app to.
Christina, are there any specific questions on any of these screens that you had when it comes to design?
I think I need to look through it before any questions arise.
So yeah, none, none exactly right now.
I guess one clarifying question.
is related to like UX versus design. My understanding is that like...
What I'm providing is more direction related to like color type layout and the actual UX like.
I don't know, the specifics of button placement or the order of things or flow. Rob, you and your team are more going to be determining that. Is that correct?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
You're pretty much just telling us what the duck looks like and how to draw it properly. Yap.
Great. That's all I can do.
Yeah.
Because I think we're pretty happy with how the UX is looking so far. I mean, this is, this game is so simple. And there, the few changes that we made, I think have been really helpful. But yeah, when it comes to like backgrounds and logos, fonts, all that stuff, Christina, I think having a few screens from you being able to flavor everything else is going to be really important.
Yap.
Yeah, one question is.
I...
Is about the prompt packs.
Are we, we're going to be including those in the D2C somehow?
So originally, there was that challenges section where you could pick a whole bunch of different options and then inject a prompt into the wall. And we kind of pulled that back to just injecting a prompt, whether that be something custom that you write out or something from a specific list of packs, just using the current packs in the meantime.
Eric.
to help show what that might look like. So if you're a mom and you have a family wall that you run, you say, hey, I'd love to, we're sitting around, let's do some scribble prompts, or I'd love to get one out to my kids. You can do so and it would ping them and let them know there's a new prompt just for that wall in addition to the daily.
Okay.
Yeah, I was just asking because, um...
It.
could have some, like we could design something. With that, I know like we leaned really heavily on the illustrations for the B2B. I imagine we won't for this, but.
Probably not to start. I think you're correct there. I think in the future, it's something that we can embrace in the same way. Like the first version of B2B, we didn't do so much with that. But then when we did the newer version, we're like, let's really create almost mini brands around each of these themes, these packs. And that's what people responded to. So we could do that in the future with like family stuff. Licensed stuff is probably going to end up being big for this.
Yeah.
Yap.
you know, the Disney pack, if that ever happens, stuff like that. So it, you know, I reference heads up a lot, which is that game where people hold the phone up and you have to guess just what is. What they've done is something similar to what I want to do, where they've got these licensed things for, you know, Marvel and Disney World and all this stuff.
prompts, well, those are just names, so it's like Iron Man or whatever. But in the future, in the same way that we're talking with Patagonia about creating outdoor prompts or Rich in the past about creating emotional intelligence prompts, we'd probably do the same.
Always out though.
Yap.
Um...
And...
This is a super general question, but just to clarify, the users for this, we're envisioning like teen and up, right? Like that's who we're designing for.
For the current version, yes.
Like, not kids' kids, well, even though kids can use it.
His kids will be able to like use it with parental permission, but yeah, the focus that Helen really wanted to stick with is, you know, teen, tween, and then, you know, bridging that generational gap with parents and grandparents.
I did.
Okay.
Which is, I mean, I was telling them yesterday, my 7 year old niece called me, she was all excited. She found a book that gives you a blank canvas with a single line already drawn on it. And then you have to add to that and write a story around that. And she was all excited to do that every single day. And you know, she's only seven years old and she kind of understands it. So goal is to get everybody on there eventually.
All right. So did you want to take some time to digest, Christina? And then you and I can hop on at some point very quickly and just kind of go through and make a few decisions on which screens you're going to do. And then
Sir, any way on them?
Yeah, we can meet, I mean, as soon as soon as you want.
I feel like I have a pretty good idea. It sounds like the login, logout screens, canvas, and the home screen for sure.
Um...
And I would, I would only ask that the the shareable screen.
And yeah, if you want.
Would that be like the screen that shows you your art that you could then download?
Yes, the one that goes out into the world like we have for the BKB. Yep.
Four.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And.
Yeah, if you, I mean, if you want, we can like chat for a few right after this and like talk about some design.
Awesome.
Yeah, let's do that. I'll send you, I'll send you my uh my Zoom link just in case Matt's on the other line.
Direction stuff, OK.
Okay. And Rob, if it's okay with you, maybe once I like have a chance to look through everything in more detail and I get into the design, I might reach out with questions.
Perfectly fine. I mean, that's why I'm here. That's why I said, just send me a link to your Figma board. You can even put it up on there. And yeah, we can kind of go back and forth through there as well as e-mail. And then just let me know if you want me to schedule another meeting too or schedule another meeting. My calendar is very open right now. And like next, the start of next month is when my next project starts.
Okay.
Dave.
So at that point, I'll have a lot more on my calendar. So right now I'm very open. So I was asking Claude what happened because the prompts pack thing wasn't showing up anymore. And so let's just see how this goes. I don't know, but we'll see how this goes. But so we've got today showing up, but then hey, I want to pick from this prompt pick. So pick prompts.
So now here it was from like the list that you guys have given us. So say we're going to do the new year here, a bad habit. I'm going to pick this, add this one wall of the day. So now I can see that it shows up right here, not drawn yet. So now click on this. So now it was a bad habit that I would like to change.
Whatever. Orange line. Cool. Orange line.
I don't think it fixed getting it. Yeah, okay. So that was the one problem that it had was it wasn't going back to the proper thing when it was done. But yeah, so it does have now like this little pick prompt thing. So I don't know if that's like how we want this, where we want that, if that should be like its own thing. Let me take that screenshot and send that over as well.
Mhm.
Or if you actually, if you want to take a screenshot so you can throw it up on the board because it said I had trouble sharing. Yes, there's the pick up prompts thing if you guys want to also like play around with how you guys envisioning doing that too.
Awesome. Yeah, and I think, you know, the functionality-wise, that's awesome. I think very little change when it comes to how it looks for now, and then in the future we will build that out so that it's something like really cool and interactive that people can use to put their own prompts. Is there an option there for people to write their own prompts?
I had that, I said, I mean the old challenge system had that. I can add that back in if that's what we want to.
Yeah, I'd say at the top of that list that pops up if there's the ability to write your own or then pick from below that, that would be ideal.
At.
That's even easier. Yes, I like that too. Cool. I will easily add that recording. Beautiful. So I'll put that as another option, pick from prompts or write your own, maybe, and that's what this says. Yeah, I can get that added. That's easy.
Awesome.
Yap.
All right, well, that's what I had. So if you guys want to go, yeah, just let me know. And then, yeah, schedule new meetings through e-mail, Figma, whatever. Just let me know. I'll be there.
Yeah, we'll spend a day or two wrapping our heads around this and getting started and get back to you and meet again.
Awesome.
Cool. Awesome. Well, have a great day, everybody. All right. All right. Bye.
Thanks, Rob.
Awesome. Thank you, Rob.
You too, bye.